crossrider.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy - Crossrider Extensions

#### PRIVACY POLICY  
CROSSRIDER.COM

Version Date: 12/31/2012  
Thank you for visiting www.crossrider.com (together with all content on the site including sub-domains and other websites operated by Crossrider Advanced Technologies Ltd. or its affiliates ( **“Crossrider”** and the **“Site”** respectively). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) explaining our online information practices about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy applies also to information that Crossrider collects and receives from visitors or users of the Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use available at http://crossrider.com/pages/terms.

 **Consent and Modification**

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Crossrider's processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use our Site and/or any of our services. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time, which change will be effective 10 days following posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of our Site 10 days following such posting shall mean that you have accepted and agreed to be bound by those changes to the Privacy Policy.

 **Introduction**

We respect your privacy online and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (" **Personal Information** ") you share with us. 

“ **Personal Information** ” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical address, an email address or other contact information.   
Any information, video, image, data, text, documents, or other content posted at your direction onto a public area of the Site becomes publicly published content and will be available to all users of the Site even if such content contains Personal Information. Please note that if you publish your contact information, you may receive unsolicited messages from users and visitors to the Site. We encourage you to publish only information you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone.  
Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with certain products and services given through the Site (including the cross-browser extensions services), you must create an account ( **“Account”** ) and provide us with your email address, a password that you will use for your Account and other specified information. 

Certain products and services given through the Site may require a fee. In order to use such services you will be required to pay an applicable fee as published on the Site. We may use a third party payment processing company in order to collect such fee and you will be required to provide such third party certain personally identifiable information such as your name, billing address and credit card information. Such third party's use of such information will be governed by its privacy policy provided, however, that we use reasonable commercial efforts to limit such third party's from using your information for any other purpose.

 **Consent**

By submitting your information through the Site and/or the use of its services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information, including Personal Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **The Way We Use Personal Information or Anonymous Information**

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site and/or its services, then we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site's services that you are authorized to access.

We may transfer your Personal Information within Crossrider or to Crossrider's third-party authorized service providers, but only to provide or to offer you services through the Site and to personalize your experience on the services. Note that your information may be transferred to other jurisdictions worldwide, including the US. 

We may provide Personal Information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other third parties for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf mainly for statistic purposes. We require that such parties maintain the confidentiality of such information.

We may also use your email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding our services. You may choose not to receive email of this type by following the unsubscribe link contained in the email provided, however, that you will not be able to opt out of receiving notifications regarding systems updates, service announcements or other administrative messages regarding the site's services (including the cross-browser extensions services). 

We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site and its services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce any agreements we may have with you including investigations of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues, (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Crossrider, its users, yourself or the public, (v) to respond to claims that any content published on the Site or the services violates any right of a third-party, (vi) to respond to claims that unauthorized information (e.g. phone number, name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Site or the services, (vii) when Crossrider is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Crossrider, (viii) pursuant to your approval, in order to supply certain services you have requested from Crossrider, (ix) to let our partners, affiliates and authorized service providers to serve you with commercials, or (x) to collect, hold and manage your Personal Information through a third party's cloud based services, as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in countries outside of your jurisdiction, including but not limited to the United States of America. 

We, independently and/or via our authorized service providers, may collect Anonymous Information (as defined below) during the use of the Site and its services including when you use any Extensions (as defined in the Developer's Agreement) downloaded from Crossrider's servers. We may use Anonymous Information or disclose it to third party service providers, to improve our services, to enhance your experience with the Site and its services and to offer new services of Crossrider from time to time. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeted advertisements.  
Anonymous Information means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated and analytics information about the use of our Site and the use of the Site's services (like any Extensions generated on Crossrider's servers) including but not limited to user's browser type, operating system type and user's IP address.

 **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

When you access or use the Site, Crossrider may use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" and Flash (or similar technologies) which stores certain information on your computer ("Local Storage") and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your experience on the Site and its services much more convenient and effortless. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. The cookies used by the Site are created per session, does not include any information about you. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them, how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. However, if you block or erase cookies, or change the settings of Flash, your online experience may be limited. 

**Choice**

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Crossrider. The notices we will provide where Crossrider collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. 

**Access/Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Crossrider wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may check your profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information we have. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites**

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site or through our services. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. Third-party cookies usually store only Anonymous Information, such as the web pages you have visited, the duration of your browsing, etc. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. Please be advised that such third party websites are independent from the Site, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such third party websites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites.

 **Security**

We take a great care in maintaining the security of the Site, its services and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures, including through the use of tokens and encryption mechanisms. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. 

**Children's Privacy**

The Site is not structured to attract nor intended for children under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect any Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age. If you are under the age of 18, you may not use this Site and its services and you may not provide us with any Personal Information of yours. 

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that Crossrider is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. In any of the circumstances described in this paragraph, the information will be subject to the privacy policy of the purchaser or assignee. 

**Commitment**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Crossrider's Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@crossrider.com. **While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.**

 **Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Crossrider who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to caprivacy@crossrider.com.   
Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year. 

Contact Information:

Crossrider Advanced Technologies Ltd.  
21 Ha'arba'a st.  
Tel-Aviv 65112  
Israel  
contact@crossrider.com
